DIEGO RIBEIRO

Front-End Web Developer

CONTACT ME

647-9075734 Toronto, ON contact@juandiegocodes.com Portfolio: www.juandiegocodes.com @juandiegocodes www.linkedin.com/in/ribeirojuan www.github.com/juandiegocodes

ABOUT ME

I'm a Toronto based front-end developer and graduate of the HackerYou Web
Development Immersive Program. With a background in Engineering and Administration,

I love to use my problem-solving skills to build creative and responsive Web applications that are accessible for all users. Constantly challenging myself to think outside the box,

I have strong experience working independently on projects and meeting targets as well as being accountable for my team's success as a Team Lead.

EDUCATION

HackerYou

Web Development Immersive Certificate 2019

Lambton College

Advanced Project Management & Strategic Leadership Post Graduate Diploma 2016-2018

Universidad Autonoma de Guadalajara, Mexico

Bachelor of Electronics and Communications Engineering 2009-2012

EXPERIENCE

• SNPS/ 1-800-Got-Junk? Senior Administrative Support June 2016 - June 2019

Team lead for the transition to the Salesforce software. Trained 20+ new department hires in the company's processes and daily tasks, such as, Salesforce Revenue report, data entry, commercial and customer enquiries.

 Project Management Office - I&IT Cluster (Ontario Ministry of Education)
 I&IT QA Project Assistant (Co-op) Sept 2017 - Dec 2017

Worked with project teams to ensure project deliverables were consistent with the appropriate Quality Assurance and Quality Control requirements and government and ministry standards.

Created and updated SharePoint Sites to all the new projects within the project portfolio of the ministry.

• Halliburton - Mexico MWD / LWD Field Engineer - Team Leader

Led the Installation, interpretation, and surveillance of electronic sensors. Monitored in real time the data obtained through the use of drilling tools to get variables such as Pressure, Gamma, and resistivity.

VOLUNTEER

Canada Learning Code Mentor

Provided guidance and motivational support to groups of 30+ students learning the fundamentals of web design, assisting with technical issues and challenges as needed.

HackerYou (Juno College of Technology) Mentor

Provided guidance and motivational support to groups of 50+ students learning the fundamentals of web development, assisting with technical issues and challenges as needed

SKILLS

- HTML5. CSS3. Sass
- Javascript, ¡Query & React
- APIs & Firebase
- Responsive Design & Website accessibility.
- Version Control and Collaborations using Git and Github
- Paired and Group programming.
- Vscode, snippets and Emmet

LANGUAGES

- English
- Spanish
- Portuguese